Office of the Vice President for Business and Finance records, 1950-ongoing UA.10.01.0003
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 81-81.
  - T. Rowe Price Associates, Inc. -- Reports, Sept. 1977-Dec. 1977 (Box 36)
  - Telephone System, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Thompson, Ogletree, Haynesworth and Deakins, 1969-1970 (Box 36)
  - Thompson, Ogletree, Haynesworth and Deakins, 1971 (Box 36)
  - Thompson, Ogletree and Deakins, 1972-1973 (Box 36)
  - Traffic Appeals Committee, 1977-1979 (Box 36)
  - Traffic Commission, 1973-1977 (Box 36)
  - Triangle Universities Computation Center (TUCC), 1977 (Box 36)
  - Union -- Local 77, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Union -- Local 465, 1977 (Box 36)
  - University Counsel (McDonald), 1977 (Box 36)
  - University Stores, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Vehicle Repair Committee, 1977 (Box 36)
  - WDBS, 1968-1974 (Box 36)
  - WDBS, 1977 (Box 36)
  - WDBS -- Managerial Board Minutes, 1973-1974 (Box 36)
  - Whitehead Medical Research Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 36)
  - Whitehead Medical Research Institute, 1976-1977 (Box 36)
  - Word Processing, 1977 (Box 36)
  - Zoology, Dept. of, 1967-1977 (Box 36)
- Accession 83-57.
  Contains Medical Center and Duke Hospital records from 1970-1974.
  - Medical Center Committee -- Meeting, Aug. 22, 1974 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center -- Correspondence -- Henry Rauch, 1974 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital, 1973-1974 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital -- Construction Feasibility Study, 1973 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital -- Construction (Duke Hospital North), 1970-1972 (Box 37)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital -- Construction (Duke Hospital North), 1973, [2 folders] (Box 37)
  - Medical Center -- Duke Hospital --- Construction (Duke Hospital North), 1974, [2 folders] (Box 37)
- Accession 86-51
  Contains subject files of Charles B. Huestis. Materials mostly concerning Business and Finance Division Conferences, the American Dance Festival (ADF), and trade unions at the university, AFSCME Local 77 and the International Union of Operating Engineers Local 456.
  - Administrative Systems Advisory Council, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1978-1983 (Box 45)
  - American Dance Festival (ADF), 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - American Dance Festival (ADF), 1979 (Box 45)
  - American Dance Festival (ADF), 1980-1984 (Box 45)
  - Associated Students of Duke University (ASDU), 1981-1983 (Box 45)
  - Athletic Council, 1980-1981 (Box 45)
  - Athletic Council, 1982-1983 (Box 45)
  - Board of Trustees -- Business and Finance Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 45)
  - Board of Trustees -- Subcommittee on Athletics, 1979-1982 (Box 45)
  - Business Auxiliaries (Asst. Bus. Mgr. Pietrantoni), 1980-1984 (Box 45)
  - Business and Finance Advisory Committee, 1982-1985 (Box 45)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Management Trainee Program (MTP)/Internship, 1982-1984 (Box 45)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Off-site Conference, 1977-1978 (Box 45)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Off-site Conference, 1979 (Box 45)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Off-site Conference, 1980-1981 (Box 45)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Off-site Conference, 1983 (Box 45)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Off-site Conference, 1984 (Box 45)
  - Central Campus Housing, 1983-1984 (Box 45)
  - Chapel, 1980-1984 (Box 45)
  - Committees -- Misc., 1980-1984 (Box 45)
  - Committee on Social Implications of Duke's Investment Policy, 1978-1981 (Box 45)
  - Conflict of Interest Committee, 1978-1984 (Box 45)
  - Data Processing, 1980-1983 (Box 45)
  - Deferred Maintenance, 1979-1984 (Box 45)
  - Dormitory -- New, 1977-1982 (Box 45)
  - Dormitory -- New, 1983-1984 (Box 45)
  - Duke University Environmental Concerns Committee (DUECC), 1979-1982 (Box 45)
  - Educational Facilities Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 45)
  - Energy, 1974-1978 (Box 45)
  - Energy, 1979-1983 (Box 46)
  - Energy Conservation, 1980-1982 (Box 46)
  - Faculty Club, 1978-1981 (Box 46)
  - Flowers Drive Failure ("Black Hole"), 1984 (Box 46)
  - Hamner, Clay -- Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box 46)
  - Interstate 40 and the Durham Expressway, 1976-1984 (Box 46)
  - Investments, 1979-1984 (Box 46)
  - Iron Dukes, 1978-1984 (Box 46)
  - Kreps, Juanita -- Correspondence, 1978-1984 (Box 46)
  - Landscape Consultants, 1983-1984 (Box 46)
  - Litton Industries, 1981 (Box 46)
  - Materials Support, 1980-1984 (Box 46)
  - Medical Center -- Health Affairs (V.P. Anlyan), 1979-1984 (Box 46)
  - National Association of College and University Business Officers (NACUBO), 1980-1983 (Box 46)
  - Physical Plant, 1980-1982 (Box 46)
  - Physical Plant, 1983-1985 (Box 46)
  - Provost (P. Griffiths), 1983-1984 (Box 46)
  - Rauch, Henry, 1978-1984 (Box 46)
  - Real Estate Development Corp., 1981-1983 (Box 46)
  - Retirement, 1978-1984 (Box 46)
  - Sea Level Hospital, 1979-1984 (Box 46)
  - Sponsored Programs, Office of, 1980-1985 (Box 46)
  - Stationary Review Committee, 1980-1983 (Box 46)
  - Traffic Appeals Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 46)
  - Traffic Commission -- Membership, 1980-1984 (Box 46)
  - Traffic Commission, 1982-1984 (Box 46)
  - Treasurer (S. C. Harward), 1980-1984 (Box 46)
  - Triangle Universities Computation Center (TUCC), 1978-1984 (Box 46)
  - Tuition and Financial Aid, 1977-1984 (Box 46)
  - Unions -- Local 77, 1978-1982 (Box 47)
  - Unions -- Local 77, 1983 (Box 47)
  - Unions -- Local 77, 1983 (Box 47)
  - Unions -- Local 465, 1978-1980 (Box 47)
  - Unions -- Local 465, 1982-1984 (Box 47)
- Accession 95-116.
  Contains departmental personnel audits, information on high level administrative searches and appointments, and records from the Human Resources office. This series dates from 1972 to 1985 (bulk 1978 and 1985). This series consists primarily of correspondence between Huestis and other university officials, especially the University Architect, University Council, Business Manager, Corporate and University Controllers, and President Terry Sanford. Several folders are dedicated to the patenting process of Duke's Dr. F. F. Jobsis's NIROS-scope invention. Also includes some Board of Trustees and Duke Endowment materials, as well as records from the Marine Lab, Internal Audit Office, Human Resource Department and the Research Triangle Foundation.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  - Academic Council -- Correspondence, 1978-1985 (Box 38)
  - Alumni Travel Coordinator (Trish Robertson), 1980-1983 (Box 38)
  - Architect, University (Ward), 1980 (Box 38)
  - Architect, University (Ward), 1981-1982 (Box 38)
  - Architect, University (Nelson), 1983-1985 (Box 38)
  - Art, Dept. of, 1980-1982 (Box 38)
  - Athletic Director (Butters), 1980-1982 (Box 38)
  - Audit Committee, 1984 (Box 38)
  - Banks, 1980-1982 (Box 38)
  - Blacknall House, 1977-1984 (Box 38)
  - Blueprint, 1983 (Box 38)
  - Board of Trustees -- Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 38)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Committee, 1980-1985 (Box 38)
  - Board of Trustees -- Executive Committee -- Meeting, January 25, 1985 - March 1-2, 1985 (Box 38)
  - Botany Dept., 1979-1984 (Box 38)
  - R. B. Brunemann Inc., 1984 (Box 38)
  - Bryan Center, 1976-1982 (Box 38)
  - Budget -- Zero-Based, 1978-1982 (Box 38)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 38)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, 1983-1985 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Advisory Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Advisory Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Correspondence and Misc., 1975-1983 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Management Audits, 1979-1980 (Box 38)
    Business and Finance Division -- Management Audits materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Off-site Conference, 1975 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Off-site Conference, 1982 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Ombudsmen Program, 1979-1980 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Ombudsmen Program, 1981-1982 (Box 38)
  - Business and Finance Div. -- Personnel, 1974 (Box 38)
    Business and Finance Division -- Personnel materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Business and Finance Report, 1977-1981 (Box 38)
  - Business Manager (Henderson), 1980 (Box 39)
  - Business Manager (Henderson), 1981-1982 (Box 39)
  - Business Manager (Henderson), 1983 (Box 39)
  - Business Manager (Henderson) (Box 39)
  - Cameron Indoor Stadium (Box 39)
  - Card Gym, "1979-1983 (Box 39)
  - Cemetery Committee, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Chancellor (Pye), 1979-1982 (Box 39)
  - Chapel, 1980-1984 (Box 39)
  - Charter Aircraft, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Chemistry, Dept. of, 1978-1981 (Box 39)
  - The Chronicle, 1980-1982 (Box 39)
  - Communications, 1979-1981 (Box 39)
  - Communications, 1982-1985 (Box 39)
  - Community and Family Medicine (Community Health Sciences), Dept. of, 1967-1982 (Box 39)
  - Computer Science, 1979 (Box 39)
  - Conflict of Interest, 1982 (Box 39)
  - Contracts, 1975-1983 (Box 39)
  - Controller, Corporate (Fuller), 1980 (Box 39)
  - Controller, Corporate (Fuller), 1981 (Box 39)
  - Controller, Corporate (Fuller) (Box 39)
  - Controller, University (Adcock), 1980 (Box 39)
  - Controller, University (Adcock) (Box 39)
  - Controller, University (Adcock), 1983 (Box 39)
  - Controller, University (Adcock) (Box 40)
  - Day Care (Box 40)
  - Data Processing (office automation and computing) (Box 40)
  - Development (Institutional Advancement), Office of, 1980 (Box 40)
  - Development (Institutional Advancement), Office of, 1981 (Box 40)
  - Development, Office of (University) (Box 40)
  - Dimensions, 1980 (Box 40)
  - Directions for Progress (Box 40)
  - Duke Endowment, 1981-1982 (Box 40)
  - Duke Homesites (Box 40)
  - Duke University Computer Kamp (DUCK), 1981 (Box 40)
  - Duke University Marine Lab -- Abrogation Document, 1979 (Box 40)
  - Duke University Marine Lab, 1980-1981 (Box 40)
  - Duke University Marine Lab, 1982-1985 (Box 40)
  - Duke University Press, 1980-1983 (Box 40)
  - Durham Chamber of Commerce, 1979-1983 (Box 40)
  - East Campus, 1979-1983 (Box 40)
  - East Campus Gym, 1978-1980 (Box 40)
  - Energy Management Advisory Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 40)
  - Engineering, School of, 1979-1983 (Box 40)
  - Engineering Library Building, 1982 (Box 40)
  - Faculty Commons, 1982-1983 (Box 40)
  - Faculty Compensation Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 40)
  - Financial Aid, 1978-1979 (Box 41)
  - Financial Aid, 1980-1984 (Box 41)
  - Finch-Yeager Building, 1979-1983 (Box 41)
    Finch-Yeager Building materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Food Service, 1980-1983 (Box 41)
  - Forest History Society, 1983-1984 (Box 41)
  - Forestry (and Environmental Studies), School of, 1979-1985 (Box 41)
  - Fuqua School of Business (Graduate School of Business Administration), 1978-1980 (Box 41)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1981-1983 (Box 41)
  - Garden Street Mall Project, 1976 (Box 41)
  - Gothic Bookstore, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Graduate School, 1978-1980 (Box 41)
  - Hazardous Waste, 1980-1981 (Box 41)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, Dept. of, 1980-1983 (Box 41)
  - Higher Education General Information Survey (HEGIS), 1976-1981 (Box 41)
  - Highland Hospital, 1978-1981 (Box 41)
  - Hotel (Washington Duke) Construction, 1979-1981 (Box 41)
  - Hotel (Washington Duke) Construction, 1982-1984 (Box 41)
  - Housing, 1979-1984 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Advisory Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Benefits and Records, 1979-1984 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Conferences, 1982 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Director (Toby Kahr), 1984-1985RESTRICTED> (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Educational Assistance Program, 1983-1984 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Employee Assistance Program, 1979-1982 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Employee Awards Banquet, 1982-1983 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Employee Relations, 1981-1983 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Employee Services, 1979-1983 (Box 41)
  - Human Resources -- Employment Office, 1980-1985 (Box 42)
  - Human Resources -- Grievances, 1980-1983 (Box 42)
    Human Resources -- Grievances materials are RESTRICTED.
  - Human Resources -- Misc., 1979-1984 (Box 42)
  - Human Resources -- Opportunity Development Center (ODC), 1980-1984 (Box 42)
  - Human Resources -- PERMIS Computer System, 1982-1983 (Box 42)
  - Human Resources -- Wage and Salary, 1980-1983 (Box 42)
  - Human Resources -- Work Rules, 1982 (Box 42)
  - Insurance, 1980-1981 (Box 42)
  - Inventory Overview Committee, 1980-1981 (Box 42)
  - Investment Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 42)
  - Internal Audit Office, 1980 (Box 42)
  - Internal Audit Office, 1981 (Box 42)
  - Internal Audit Office, 1982-1984, [5 folders] (Box 42)
  - Job Enhancement Program, 1984 (Box 43)
  - Law School, 1979-1985 (Box 43)
  - Library, 1978-1983 (Box 43)
  - Medicine, School of, 1981 (Box 43)
  - Nursing, School of, 1978-1979 (Box 43)
  - Patent Administration Office, 1979-1980 (Box 43)
  - Patent Administration, Office of, 1982-1984 (Box 43)
  - Patent Administration, Office of -- NIROS-scope (Dr. F.F. Jobsis), 1979-1981 (Box 43)
  - Patent Administration, Office of -- NIROS-scope (Dr. F.F. Jobsis), 1982-1984 (Box 43)
  - Personnel (Acting Director J. Linn), 1980-1981 (Box 43)
  - Personnel -- Wage and Salary Administration, 1976-1978 (Box 43)
  - Personnel Policy Committee, 1980-1982 (Box 43)
  - Physics, Dept. of, 1978-1984 (Box 43)
  - Policies and Procedures, 1987-1982 (Box 43)
  - Procurement System, 1981 (Box 43)
  - President (Terry Sanford), 1980-1981 (Box 43)
  - President (Terry Sanford), 1982-1983 (Box 43)
  - President (Terry Sanford), 1984-1985 (Box 43)
  - President (Terry Sanford) -- Monthly Report to Trustees, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
  - Project Pride, 1977-1982 (Box 43)
  - Provost (Bevan), 1979-1982 (Box 43)
  - Psychiatry, Dept. of, 1980,1983 (Box 43)
  - Psychical Research Foundation, 1978-1980 (Box 43)
  - Psychology, Dept. of, 1979-1982 (Box 43)
  - Public Policy Studies, Dept. of, 1980-1984 (Box 43)
  - Racquet Club, 1980-1984 (Box 43)
  - Real Estate, 1972, 1978-1979 (Box 43)
  - Real Estate, 1980-1982 (Box 43)
  - Real Estate, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
  - Real Estate -- Howard Ford Property, 1982-1984 (Box 43)
  - Real Estate -- Riverbend Property, 1983 (Box 43)
  - Recycling and Surplus Sales, 1980-1983 (Box 43)
  - Renovations -- Baldwin Auditorium, 1978-1982 (Box 43)
  - Renovations -- Crowell Building, 1980-1982 (Box 43)
  - Renovations -- Flowers/Union Buildings, 1981-1983 (Box 43)
  - Renovations -- Misc., 1978-1982 (Box 44)
  - Renovations -- Page Auditorium, 1978-1984 (Box 44)
  - Renovations -- Physical Education Facilities, 1979-1980 (Box 44)
  - Renovations -- Physics Building, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Renovations -- Service Complex, 1979-1980 (Box 44)
  - Renovations -- Sociology/Psychology Building, 1981 (Box 44)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 44)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 44)
  - Research Triangle Foundation, 1983-1984 (Box 44)
  - Safety, 1979-1984 (Box 44)
  - SHUR (System for Hospital Uniform Reporting), 1979-1980 (Box 44)
  - Soccer, 1983 (Box 44)
  - Student Affairs, 1979-1983 (Box 44)
  - Student Affairs, 1984-1985 (Box 44)
  - Student Loans, 1978 (Box 44)
  - Stores, 1978-1983 (Box 44)
  - Surveys (multi-institutional), 1978-1984 (Box 44)
  - Talent Identification Program (TIP), 1980-1981 (Box 44)
  - TIAA/CREF, 1978-1983 (Box 44)
  - Tennis facilities, 1979-1984 (Box 44)
  - Track, 1978-1981 (Box 44)
  - Transportation, 1980-1983 (Box 44)
  - United Way, 1980-1983 (Box 44)
  - University Counsel (McDonald), 1980-1981 (Box 44)
  - University Counsel (McDonald), 1982-1983 (Box 44)
  - University Counsel (McDonald), 1984-1985 (Box 44)
  - University Relations (VP/Dir. Green), 1980-1983 (Box 44)
  - Venture Capital, 1982-1983 (Box 44)
  - WDBS, 1981-1984 (Box 44)
  - Whitehead Medical Research Institute, 1978-1982 (Box 44)
  - Zoology, Dept of, 1978-1983 (Box 44)
- Accession A98-32
  This accession contains records documenting activities of the Business and Finance Division of the University, including records of the offices of the Business Manager, Treasurer, Comptroller, and Vice-President. There are files that pre-date the 1962 formation of the division, but which document functions latter carried out by it. The records include correspondence, audits, cost studies, reports, financial records, statistics, personnel information, and other material. Major subjects include administration of grants and endowments from the Ford Foundation, the W.K. Kellogg Foundation, the Duke Endowment, and the Doris Duke Foundation, among other funds and trusts; the fianances and operations of academic and non-academic departments, professional schools, the library, and affiliated organizations such as TUCC. Officials represented include Stephen C. Harward, G.C. Henrickson, A.S. Brower, and C.B. Huestis.
  Retained original order.
  - Doris Duke Prenatal Program and other Doris/Nanaline Duke Gifts (Paul Green Jr.) (Box 48)
  - James B. Duke Professorship Fund (Box 48)
  - Angier B. Duke Memorial, 1969 (Box 48)
  - The Duke Endowment (Henney) (Box 48)
  - Resolutions - Duke Endowment Grants for Appropriations (Box 48)
  - Duke Press -- Ford Foundation (Box 48)
  - Ford Profile, Ashmore, Frank (Box 48)
  - The Ford Foundation (College Grants) (Box 48)
  - Graduate and Research Program (Continuation of G.E.B) (Box 48)
  - IBM - Grant (Box 48)
  - Jones Chair of Engineering Fund (Edwin L. Jones Family) (Box 48)
  - W.K. Kellogg Foundation (Box 48)
  - Medical School Faculty Wives of Duke University Scholarship Fund est. Jan. 1970 (Box 48)
  - The National Foundation, 1968 (Box 48)
  - N.C. Heart Association Inc., 1968 (Box 48)
  - Henry J. Oosting Memorial Lecture (Box 48)
  - Julian M. Ruffin Research Fund, 1968 (Box 48)
  - Damon Runyon Memorial Fund for Cancer Research, Inc. (Box 48)
  - Alex H. Sands, Jr. Scholarship Fund (Box 48)
  - Southern Universities Fellowship (Danforth contribution) (Box 48)
  - United States Steel Foundation Fund, 1969 (Box 48)
  - Learning Institute of NC (Appropriation by Duke University) (Box 49)
  - Lewis, Harold - Duke University Distinguished Professors Seminar (Box 49)
  - McKinney, John C. Center for Southern Studies (Box 49)
  - Josiah Macy Jr. Foundation Transfers from Provost's Fund (Dr. Taylor Cole) (Box 49)
  - Avalon Foundation Scholarships (Box 49)
  - Ball, Margaret - Esso. Foundation Experiments to Improve the Living-Learning Environment (Box 49)
  - Warren G. Booker (Correspondence about will, taxes, etc.) (Box 49)
  - Brinkley, W.L. Guidance Associates (Box 49)
  - Cobb, Clarence - Rental Agreement with Monroe Calculating Machine Co., Inc. (Box 49)
  - The Cooperative Program in the Humanities - UNC-CH 1968 (Box 49)
  - Hanes Fund United-Medical Fund (Box 49)
  - Fredric M. Hanes Trust--Trust Investment Committee of Wachovia Bank and Trust Company (Box 49)
  - Inman Fund (Grants awarded by Medical School Committee) (Box 49)
  - IBM -- Patent Agreements (Box 49)
  - Schools, Colleges, Departments, Duke University
    - Accounting (Box 49)
    - Accounting Systems and Procedures (Box 49)
    - Accounts, Payable, Invoices, etc. (Box 49)
    - Admissions (all offices) (Box 49)
    - Aesthetics, Art, Music (Depts. Of) Art Council (Box 49)
    - Alumni Affairs (Roger Marshall) (Box 49)
    - Anatomy (Box 49)
    - Appointments Office (Box 49)
    - Army Research Ordinance Durham Building Lease (Box 49)
    - Athletic Association - Golf (Box 49)
    - Band (DU), 1950 (Box 49)
    - Biochemistry, Dept. of (Box 49)
    - Botany, DU Gardens (Box 49)
    - Central Supply Room (Box 49)
    - Chemistry, Dept. (Box 49)
    - Child Guidance Clinic (Box 49)
    - Community Health Science (Dept. of ) (Box 49)
    - Computation Center (AROD) (Box 49)
    - Cost Reduction Office -- the Idea File (Box 49)
    - Development Office (Box 49)
    - Divinity School Reports (Box 49)
    - Divinity School Reports (Box 50)
    - Education, Dept. of (Box 50)
    - Engineering School (Box 50)
    - English Dept. (Box 50)
    - Faculty Club (Box 50)
    - Forestry, School of (Box 50)
    - Geology Dept. (Box 50)
    - Gothic Bookshop (Box 50)
    - Graduate School (Box 50)
    - History Dept. (Box 50)
    - Information Services (Box 50)
    - Information Systems (Box 50)
    - Law School (Box 50)
    - Library (East and West) (Box 50)
    - Record of Sale from Duke University Library Duplicate Collection Sale (Box 50)
    - Maintenance Dept. (Box 50)
    - Correspondence - Howard, W.K. (Box 50)
    - Mathematics Dept. (Box 50)
    - School of Medicine thru 30 June 1966 (Box 50)
    - School of Medicine July 1966- (Box 50)
    - Neuropsychiatry, Dept. of (Box 50)
    - Nursing, School of (Box 50)
    - PEP (Box 51)
    - Applications - Correspondence concerning applications, updated resumes on current employees (Box 51)
    - Dept. of Pediatrics (Box 51)
    - Personnel Department, University and Hospital (Correspondence), 1963- (Box 51)
    - Pharmacy - Duke Hospital General Correspondence with I.T. Reamer and certain statistics (Box 51)
    - Dept. of Philosophy (Box 51)
    - Physical Education (Trinity and Woman's College) (Box 51)
    - Dept. of Physical Planning, 1969 (Box 51)
    - Physics Dept. (Box 51)
    - Dept. of Physiology and Pharmacology (Box 51)
    - Political Science Dept. (Box 51)
    - Post Office (United States) Lease, correspondence, etc. (Box 51)
    - Private Diagnostic Clinics (Box 51)
    - Purchasing Department (Box 51)
    - Registrar's Office, Photostatic Statistics, Reports (Box 51)
    - Religion Dept. (Box 51)
    - Romance Languages, Dept. of (Box 51)
    - Security Division (statements) (Box 51)
    - Sponsored Research (Box 51)
    - Sociology, Dept. of (Box 51)
    - Duke University Stores -- Wellons (correspondence, national assoc. of stores, etc.) (Box 51)
    - Student Activities Office (Box 51)
    - Summer School (Clyde and Petty) Japan Society Enka Foundation (Box 51)
    - Zoology Dept. (Box 51)
    - The Woman's College (Brinkley) Correspondence and misc. items concerning East Campus (Box 51)
    - Management Services (Box 51)
- Accession UA2011-0006, circa 1960s-1992; 7.5 Linear Feet; 5 boxes
  This accession contains Charles Huestis' records and includes correspondence, subject files, reports, datebooks, and other general files. This material is restricted for 25 years from date of origin. Trustee committee records are restricted 50 years from date of origin.
  - Costa Rican Property (Box 52)
  - Explorers Club Expedition Committee (Box 52)
  - Credit Card List (Box 52)
  - Christmas Letter (2 folders) (Box 52)
  - Alpine Club (Box 52)
  - Bank of America (Box 52)
  - Bills (Personal that have been paid) (Box 52)
  - Biographical Data (Charles Huestis) (Box 52)
  - Conservation, General (Box 52)
  - Insurance (Box 52)
  - Sierra Club Financial Advisory Committee (Box 52)
  - Sierra Club Reorganization Committee (Box 52)
  - Sierra Club Treasurer (Box 52)
  - Economic and Land Research Corporation (Box 52)
  - Property Research Corporation (Box 52)
  - Tom Butters (Box 52)
  - Union Activity (Box 52)
  - Meeting Notes (Box 52)
  - Athletic Department (3 folders) (Box 52)
  - Hotel (New) (3 folders) (Box 52)
  - Athletic Director (Butters) (3 folders) (Box 52)
  - Heating Plant Task Force (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Employee Considerations Calendar (Box 53)
  - Achievement Award (Box 53)
  - Administrative Oversite Department (Box 53)
  - Athletic Department (Box 53)
  - Gene McDonald (Box 53)
  - Bill Anlyan (Box 53)
  - Tom Butters (Box 53)
  - John Costlow (Box 53)
  - Paul Dumas (Box 53)
  - Phillip Griffiths (Box 53)
  - Steve Harward (Box 53)
  - Jim Henderson (Box 53)
  - Toby Kahr (Box 53)
  - Marine Lab (Box 53)
  - North Carolina Nature Conservancy (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Terry Sanford (Box 53)
  - American Edwards Lab (Box 53)
  - Aquatics (Box 53)
  - Management Interns (2 folders) (Box 53)
  - Recommendations (Box 53)
  - Special Projects (Box 53)
  - Public Safety (Box 53)
  - Football (Box 53)